Hello, everyone! I'm Mona Tsunagai.
EASY JAPANESE is brought to you from Sendai.
Today, I'd like to ask people in Sendai what they think about Japan.
Hello! Today, I'd like to ask people in Sendai what they think about Japan.
What I think about Japan?
Yes! What I think about Japan.
As for fish, the freshest fish in Japan is around the sea.
It's best to catch fresh fish whenever you can.
In Japan, the food is delicious.
sdcgfjh
What's your favorite food in Japan?
Rice?
Yes, rice.
I like Japanese food.
You're getting a lot of attention for your health.
Yes.
I like miso soup.
That's true.
Hello!
Hello.
Today, I'd like to ask people what they think about Japan.
What do you think is good about Japan?
There are a lot of women who look good with black hair.
Do you mean women with black hair?
Yes, I think women with long black hair are the most beautiful.
They are considerate.
That's nice.
Do you feel that in your daily life?
They are kind.
They are very kind to the elderly.
They have a kind heart.
Considerate.
That's a word I'd like to spread abroad.
That's right.
The word considerate can be used for anything.
For example, going to a restaurant and eating without leaving anything behind is considerate.
Taking care of people is considerate.
I think the word considerate can be used for anything.
That's nice.
That's true.
How should I put it?
Considerate for people.
That kind of thing can be put into one word.
For example, even if it snows, there are about 10 types of snow.
There is a type of snow called Sasame snow.
There is a type of snow called Awa snow.
I don't think there are any other countries that have such rich expressions.
What do you think are the good things about Japan?
Something that comes out of nowhere.
Anime.
I think it's anime.
I can't think of anything.
Anime.
Do you like anime?
I don't really like it, but I don't think there are any other countries that have it.
Anime culture.
Otaku culture.
For example, what kind of anime do you like?
Dragon Ball.
Doraemon.
Yes, Doraemon.
Dragon Ball.
By the way, today we are conscious of pre-cure.
Pre-cure.
We are conscious of pre-cure.
Like this.
Haikyuu.
Kuromachi.
The latest anime.
Otake.
What do you think is bad about Japan?
I don't like it.
Do you?
I don't really like it.
What is it?
I only look at my cell phone.
Alchism.
The language has been disordered recently.
When we were young, the word yabai was a word used by yakuza.
So that has changed.
For example, irezumi.
Tattoo.
It's not different at all.
It's a sign of a criminal.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
It was perfect.
Thank you.